[{"answer": "What has come out that I can talk about today is that Trayvon Martin somehow snuck up on him and according to Mr. Crump, their own attorney, he was on -- we don't know if this is verifiable information, but he was on the phone with his girlfriend.", "docId": "120401pmt", "aSentId": 24, "question": "What did George tell you Trayvon Martin allegedly did to him?", "qSentId": 23}, {"answer": "One of those things.", "docId": "120401pmt", "aSentId": 33, "question": "What did George tell you he said?", "qSentId": 32}, {"answer": "I'd ask him why did he, in fact, pick out my son.", "docId": "120401pmt", "aSentId": 47, "question": "Tracy, if you had the chance to speak to George Zimmerman right now, what would you say to him?", "qSentId": 46}, {"answer": "And Sybrina, many believe that you are suffering perhaps even more now since losing your son by the attempt by some people to assassinate his character, to bring up all this stuff about his behavior at school and so on which portrays him in a very damaging light.", "docId": "120401pmt", "aSentId": 55, "question": "And how does he feel about taking my son's life?", "qSentId": 54}, {"answer": "It bothers me as a mother to hear all of those negative things about my son.", "docId": "120401pmt", "aSentId": 57, "question": "What do you say to that?", "qSentId": 56}, {"answer": "You know, I'm a parent.", "docId": "120401pmt", "aSentId": 80, "question": "What did you make of what they were saying?", "qSentId": 79}, {"answer": "I mean it's really important, it seems to me, that you have to allow the legal process to take its course.", "docId": "120401pmt", "aSentId": 111, "question": "But it's just one of those situations where every parent in America, in the world, would say what -- what happened?", "qSentId": 110}, {"answer": "We're bringing back the Wild West.", "docId": "120401pmt", "aSentId": 127, "question": "Even if they had a fight, that doesn't give you the right to pull out a gun and shoot him in the street, does it?", "qSentId": 126}, {"answer": "I experienced it for the first time with the Commodores.", "docId": "120401pmt", "aSentId": 172, "question": "Aware of it?", "qSentId": 171}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120401pmt", "aSentId": 222, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 221}, {"answer": "I understand.", "docId": "120401pmt", "aSentId": 233, "question": "You understand?", "qSentId": 232}, {"answer": "You're moving -- because I think about you -- you had all the Commodore stuff, and that's enough for most people.", "docId": "120401pmt", "aSentId": 248, "question": "ICHIE: Am I moving you?", "qSentId": 247}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120401pmt", "aSentId": 259, "question": "Is he annoyed?", "qSentId": 258}, {"answer": "It would be \"Easy\" or \"All Night Long.\"", "docId": "120401pmt", "aSentId": 276, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 275}, {"answer": "I am a hopeless romantic.", "docId": "120401pmt", "aSentId": 317, "question": "Are you for real a sensitive, romantic, loving kind of guy?", "qSentId": 316}, {"answer": "God, you would ask that question.", "docId": "120401pmt", "aSentId": 331, "question": "How many times have you been properly in love in your life?", "qSentId": 330}, {"answer": "I do remember.", "docId": "120401pmt", "aSentId": 336, "question": "Do you remember her?", "qSentId": 335}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120401pmt", "aSentId": 339, "question": "Do I have to say that loud?", "qSentId": 338}, {"answer": "And I should say there was one more.", "docId": "120401pmt", "aSentId": 347, "question": "And how old was she?", "qSentId": 346}, {"answer": "Well, you know, you think a little bit more before you say I love you.", "docId": "120401pmt", "aSentId": 367, "question": "In what sense?", "qSentId": 366}, {"answer": "That you have to throw yourself into it.", "docId": "120401pmt", "aSentId": 374, "question": "ORGAN: What have you really learned about love?", "qSentId": 373}, {"answer": "Well, mine's easy.", "docId": "120401pmt", "aSentId": 384, "question": "How do you do it in your marriage?", "qSentId": 383}, {"answer": "Oh, no, it's perfect.", "docId": "120401pmt", "aSentId": 396, "question": "And do they get on now?", "qSentId": 395}, {"answer": "Absolutely not.", "docId": "120401pmt", "aSentId": 405, "question": "Do you sing at these little tribal meetings?", "qSentId": 404}, {"answer": "Go on.", "docId": "120401pmt", "aSentId": 460, "question": "Well, you know the answer to that, don't you?", "qSentId": 459}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120401pmt", "aSentId": 490, "question": "Never?", "qSentId": 489}, {"answer": "Holy cow.", "docId": "120401pmt", "aSentId": 497, "question": "Who is the biggest, most romantic sexual singer you've ever deployed?", "qSentId": 496}, {"answer": "I think I understand you.", "docId": "120401pmt", "aSentId": 503, "question": "I mean, Marvin, Marvin did it for me, you understand me?", "qSentId": 502}, {"answer": "Barry White and Smokey Robinson.", "docId": "120401pmt", "aSentId": 511, "question": "Have you ever had a Barry White night?", "qSentId": 510}, {"answer": "Yes, yes.", "docId": "120401pmt", "aSentId": 514, "question": "You know what I'm saying?", "qSentId": 513}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120401pmt", "aSentId": 517, "question": "You know?", "qSentId": 516}, {"answer": "I understand.", "docId": "120401pmt", "aSentId": 537, "question": "You understand?", "qSentId": 536}, {"answer": "ICHIE: I understand it.", "docId": "120401pmt", "aSentId": 559, "question": "Do you understand that?", "qSentId": 558}, {"answer": "It was better than mine.", "docId": "120401pmt", "aSentId": 567, "question": "You like that?", "qSentId": 566}, {"answer": "You are going through what we call panic.", "docId": "120401pmt", "aSentId": 579, "question": "And what does the pressure of performance become like when you're going through that deterioration?", "qSentId": 578}, {"answer": "You could actually sell sheet music so you know we took over \"Endless Love,\" \"Hello,\" \"Truly.\"", "docId": "120401pmt", "aSentId": 635, "question": "Is that what you call it?", "qSentId": 634}, {"answer": "Tuskegee.", "docId": "120401pmt", "aSentId": 658, "question": "It's -- \"Tuskegee,\" right?", "qSentId": 657}, {"answer": "And the one that I love the most was, \"There's a choice we're making.", "docId": "120401pmt", "aSentId": 664, "question": "You just did a brilliant impression in the break there from the \"We are the World\" video where all these big stars got to sing one line and I said who sang the best line?", "qSentId": 663}, {"answer": "Lionel, this has been one of my favorite interviews I've ever done at CNN.", "docId": "120401pmt", "aSentId": 673, "question": "Bob, you have nothing to worry about, OK?", "qSentId": 672}, {"answer": "Swathed.", "docId": "120401pmt", "aSentId": 687, "question": "What's the word again?", "qSentId": 686}, {"answer": "Well, you know, any time you're around greatness like I was for six years and you see it at close quarters, you're asked about it.", "docId": "120401pmt", "aSentId": 743, "question": "Hank, you're getting a bit of flak for this book and what was the purpose in writing it?", "qSentId": 742}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, that's a lot of time to spend with a player.", "docId": "120401pmt", "aSentId": 754, "question": "I mean as far as coach and player goes, it doesn't get much closer than that, does it?", "qSentId": 753}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, very complex.", "docId": "120401pmt", "aSentId": 758, "question": "What do you make of him as a man?", "qSentId": 757}, {"answer": "Well, I'm certainly not the first coach that's ever written a book.", "docId": "120401pmt", "aSentId": 767, "question": "How do you respond to that?", "qSentId": 766}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, those rules are not, you know, written rules.", "docId": "120401pmt", "aSentId": 783, "question": "What's your response to him?", "qSentId": 782}, {"answer": "No, not in any way, shape or form.", "docId": "120401pmt", "aSentId": 796, "question": "Did you just think, you know what in the guy let me down, he wasn't a proper friend to me so I'm going to make money out of his intimate life and the way that you have done?", "qSentId": 795}, {"answer": "No, I couldn't, because the first, you know, inkling that there might be a problem was Mark Steinberg, Tiger's agent called me, and told me that there was going to be an article coming out in the \"National Enquirer\" but that it wasn't true.", "docId": "120401pmt", "aSentId": 819, "question": "Could you quite believe what you were hearing when all these stories began to come out?", "qSentId": 818}, {"answer": "I don't think it would be my place necessarily as a coach, but it would be my place I feel like as a friend, and I certainly would have said something, and I know Steve Williams would have said something, too.", "docId": "120401pmt", "aSentId": 824, "question": "Would you have done if you'd known?", "qSentId": 823}, {"answer": "You know, I think he's probably softened some.", "docId": "120401pmt", "aSentId": 827, "question": "Do you feel that he's changed at all since the scandal?", "qSentId": 826}, {"answer": "Well, he's definitely striking the ball well.", "docId": "120401pmt", "aSentId": 834, "question": "Could he win the Masters this year, do you think?", "qSentId": 833}]